Non-human
post staff got me 1.
Another little room is improvised,
but better than staying outside.
Your pussy there man speed please there Juninho pussy for us
that brother is pistachio bro,
come on,
come on for us,
for us.
Wow,
that's way too good.
Tamo by hand.
Ó Juninho will lend me 1 gallon which is today I rescued
this Chevette Mateus will give me 1 ride here.
O
bro,
this chevas has to take it now for god's sake,
go again.
The chevas is not rolling.
At least I managed to get a lullaby.
Go down with him here to another post.
Dude I can't stand this perrengue anymore.
Man,
it looks like it has no end.
I'm in Narnia,
you're on.
The car doesn't keep picking up,
I put five liters of fuel in addition to not deciding
the car not to pick up the door,
it dawned broken.
Then it's complicated,
see? Hand?
I need to solve this car.
Guy. It doesn't.
If you are from Jundiaí and you are a citizen,
send a message that I can't take it anymore.
There goes the Caião on foot again.
I have my partner Matthew here helping to deliver the truffles today.
Bro,
since chevas had a bad time saw brother you see bro relationship
is all bro the guy is greatest partner.
I fall there old man,
don't walk,
it's not sunny.
I'll help you there old man deliver the truffles.
Is it on?
At least it's not blurry.
Weekend.
How are you doing?
So I replaced the truffles very quickly there.
I just did the replacement thanks to God there was dry truffles in here.
bro
thank you my man with God,
we're together,
I dropped 1 for every 1 there,
huh?
Then my ally is fine so my bro is worth people.
Good weekend here we are,
huh?
My ride left and now I'm here,
oh and besides everything I've only forgotten the detail,
bro.
I have a week to find a place for me to live.
My car is broken.
What am I going to do?
I have no idea.
It's us until tomorrow.